Sophiles One Grand Prix
You have to answer the questions that the celebrity tarmo asks you instantly,
Well, you have to answer accurately and concisely, don't you?
That's important.
So, this project is here to help me improve.
Oh, I see.
Well then, here is the subject!
Let's see!
Let's see, Okanpa's school...
A boy?
Boy?
Girl. Girl.
This way!
Yes!
Oh, hey...
I don't...
If you're with me for 3 seconds, I'll like you for 5 seconds or something.
It's early, Kujiken's been doing it for a while.
Yes, yes.
Pretty for you I can't say no to a chain of events
I want to make it happen with you
On a brand new world
Hear me now If it's meaningless words, I don't need them anymore
It's a now, it's a vow
This way, please!
Let's see... a cute guy eats an apple.
The one where the cute guy eats the apple?
The one where the cute guy eats the apple. The one where the cute guy eats an apple.
How do you like it when someone says, "I'm going to eat an apple? What do you think?
I'd say, "That's a good idea.
Point taken.
Yes!
Now for the question.
Which way do we go? Masaki Togisuka
Here we go!
This way!
A mermaid falls in love with her uncle.
I don't understand.
What? What's the story of the Little Mermaid?
I only know Ariel.
But I know it.
Then you're right.
The little mermaid falls in love with the prince.
Oh, well...
It fits.
So it's safe?
Oh! Oh, my God!
I can't believe I just heard that.
I'm gonna be like, "Oh, the Little Mermaid.
I love it.
It's getting stepped on.
That's about right.
I don't think that's the right word.
That's not how you use it.
Okay, now, let's continue.
This is a service problem for Hana-chan. This is a service issue for Hana-chan.
Oh! That's not an opinion!
I'm sure you can answer it.
Really?
Here's the question!
Yes!
Yes, yes.
Let the toy boy throw the flower with his feelings.
I'm going to lie.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's the other way around.
You lie because the flower throws.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's a tough one.
It's difficult.
There are so many things I don't know anymore.
I can say it, but I can't say it.
It's a service issue.
We're trying to get a member to do what he does best.
I see.
That's great.
I'm really nervous.
You are?
Yes, I am.
Yes, I do.
I just picked out a few things that Yuzu is good at.
Oh!
Flowers. It's from a flower.
what is it?
This is Yuzu. I think it's okay.
Here we go!
Here's the subject!
Ta-da!
Uh, let's see, there's a police weirdo in Katsushika...
He does weird stuff every day.
Well, I guess that's right.
If you feel sorry for him, he's a weirdo.
You must feel sorry for him.
That's him, right? The guy with the fat eyebrows?
You don't police yourself every day, you do weird stuff.
Don't say that.
What's this?
Ceph?
Out?
Time hasn't passed
The police in Katsushika do weird stuff every day.
Yes.
Added bonus!
They said it's okay to make an extra.
Ok, ok, ok
This is for you, Ayumi.
I want you to answer me.
I want you to answer me if you have that passion of your daily life.
Oh, wait, no!
What should I do?
I think we're ready now. I think we're ready now.
You know?
Go! Let's do it.
Subject!
Oh, thank you.
I can't.
No, wait.
No, no, wait, let me finish.
Has anyone ever seen this before?
You can't hold the clock for three seconds.
It's impossible.
How many times have I told you?
Right in front of you.
You're always saying that you've never seen anything like it.
You've never seen it.
You're always talking about them to us.
He really is a tsukkebiri.
I cried a lot yesterday.
But if you like Kandra, you'll understand.
I can sum it up in 3 seconds...
Bracho! Bracho?
Bracho?
We're going back hundreds of years.
Nukunigami are going back in time.
That's the same code as the normal girl.
In the same code as that normal girl.
You can't put it all together in three seconds.
All they said was the same code.
The same code.
Abandonment, abandonment, abandonment. Abandonment. Abandonment.
what is it?
I'm curious.
We're all trying to figure it out.
We have to answer it, right?
Okay, well, the three of us picked.
It took us an hour.
One hour.
Mr. Suzuki, something's wrong, isn't it?
I don't have any hobbies.
Finally, a beautiful twist.
I've decided.
What kind?
This way.
There you go!
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
You're a ghost!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Wait a minute... Oh, no...
Oh, a ghost!
You know what?
It's true, the other day...
Yesterday, like three or two days ago.
Yesterday!
We went to see them together.
Yesterday.
A movie.
Content Mansion.I need a content apartment.
Awesome.
Why didn't you just give us a big hint already?
I gave it to you as a service question.
What's so good about it?
What's what?
You need to work on that.
But I want to give you a chance to make up for it.
What's that?
Can I give it to you?
I wrote this last one.
If I gave it a perfect score of 100...
Kaoru Momoi would be...
She's the oldest member of Ameikyoka.
I wish we could all say that.
Yes, ma'am.
Understood.
Great service!
Yes, sir.
I'll make up a penalty game.
Gradually
That's me, that's me.
McShake, right?
Yes, sir.
What? Cheap!
A McShake.
Okay, okay.
No, it's not.
I don't know.
It's a Shake Shack.That's it... at the Shake Shack.
I can't.
I really, really can't.
I really can't.
Let's go with Haagen-Dazs.
I really can't do that either.
I'm sorry, but...
Okay, then.
One piece of candy up to 200 yen.
No, 150 yen.
Oh, okay.
Kitchen
Carved for 50 years
subject
this way.
We get along well
They eat, sing and dance well
Oh, it's a penalty game.
Yes, yes, yes.
Aim, aim, aim.
Why?
You got this!
Thank you!
It's not here.
Why not?
No, I wanted you to at least answer this one.
I'm already in the middle of a service.
Why?
Don't even think about it.Don't even think about it.
This game. Oh, no.
Um, well, then, something
I might be able to tighten it up nicely.
Oh, sure.
Maybe he's not so good at closing.
Oh, I see.
So, I'm going to take responsibility this time and ask you to finish.
I'd like to recommend you as the oldest end recipient.
Good luck.
You have three seconds to close the Sokuleswan Grand Prix.
Here we go.
I'll buy all three of you 150 yen worth of snacks.
Let's go first so we can close it out.
No problem. I did my best.
I can't do anything from you.
That's enough!
Come on!